<!--
This file is to record the changes in the project that will be reported
in the release history and release announcements. It is reasonable to keep
changes relatively high level to be understandable by the users but still
reflect the main changes made in the project.
Please refer to the following link regarding the format of this file:
http://maven.apache.org/plugins/maven-changes-plugin/changes.html
Please avoid making line breaks and tabulation in the description as those 
will appear in the produced result. 
-->
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/changes-1.0.0.xsd">
	<properties>
		<title>ELK Reasoner Project</title>
	</properties>
	<body>
	    <release version="${release.version}" date="${buildDate}" description="Changes since the last release">
	    	<action dev="pavel" type="add">
				Use Protege OWL Frame List to display proofs; axioms can be edited and deleted; proofs are expanded upon triggering the explain button.
			</action>
			<action dev="pavel" type="add">
				Highlight premises if an inference is selected in the list.
			</action>
			<action dev="pavel" type="add">
				Eliminate cycles in proofs: a proof for an axiom will not use this axioms as one of the premises [owlapi-proof bundle].
			</action>
			<action dev="pavel" type="add">
				Update proof after changes in the ontologies without recomputing the proof: if an axiom is changed or removed it is removed from the asserted axioms of the proof.
			</action>	    	
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Simplify cycle elimination using convenient utilities for testing derivability [owlapi-proof bundle].
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Define an extension point for proof services; add management of proof services in the UI.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Add a manager to keep track of import closure to quickly check if an axiom is asserted.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Support axioms from import ontologies in proofs, including management of duplicate axioms.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Reuse the display setting (e.g., row expansion state, selection) for proof parts remained after proof changes.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Support axioms with annotations and adding annotations to axioms in the proofs.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Add tree-like navigation elements to the proofs UI; kept in synch with the current UI look and feel.
			</action>
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Expand and collapse rows recursively after long mouse press or ALT + click; a recursive expansion limit is used to avoid UI lockup in cases with huge proofs.
			</action>			
			<action dev="yevgeny" type="add">
				Optimize rendering of proofs after expansion/collapse/resize by caching row heights values for list width values.
			</action>			
		</release>		
	</body>
</document>